https://www.specialpipingmaterials.com/privacy-policy/

High quality exotic piping products from approved manufacturers - We are the market leaders
Contact
Language:
English
Português do Brasil
Home | Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy Statement
What information do we collect about you and how?
Special Piping Materials Ltd, as a Data Controller, is bound by the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR). We collect information about you via questionnaires, customer satisfaction surveys, email product enquiry, placing orders, giving feedback etc. We do not hold personal data only email, name and company details and will only hold this data in line with our policy on data retention.
Internet Based Advertising
We use LinkedIn, Facebook and Twitter advertising services and as such there are tracking codes installed on our website so that we can manage the effectiveness of these campaigns. We do not store any personal data within this type of tracking.
How will we use the information about you and why?
At Special Piping Materials Ltd we take your privacy seriously and our lawful reason for processing your personal information will be “To fulfil our contractual obligations with the supplier or customer” e.g. to purchase and provide the products to meet both our organisation and customer requirements. We will only use this information subject to data protection law and our duty of confidentiality.
We do not pass your information to any third-party provider, agent, subcontractor or any other associated organisation
Security precautions in place about data collected
When you give us personal information, we take steps to make sure that it’s treated securely. Non-sensitive details (your email address etc.) are sent normally over the Internet, and this can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. This will be stored on a secure local server protected with up to date security software and firewalls.
How long will we hold your data for?
We are required under UK tax law to keep your basic personal data (name, address, contact details) for a minimum of 6 years from termination of relationship.
Access to your information, correction, and deletion
What is a Subject Access Request?
This is your right to request a copy of the personal information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of your personal information, please email or write to us (address below in the ‘How to contact us’ section). We will respond to your request within one month of receipt of the request.
You may ask us to correct an inaccuracy or completely remove information we hold about you by emailing dawn@specialpipingmaterials.com or writing to the above address.
Complaints
If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact Dawn Sheppard at the address below who we will investigate the matter. However, if you are not satisfied with our response and you feel your personal data has been processed in a way that does not meet the GDPR, you have a specific right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 22nd May 2018 in line with the new GDPR guidelines.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:
By email: dawn@specialpipingmaterials.com
Or write to: Dawn Sheppard, General Manager
Address: Special Piping Materials Ltd, Globe Industrial Estate, Broadway, Dukinfield SK16 4UU.
Europe
America
Asia
Middle East
Australia
England
Special Piping Materials Ltd
Broadway, Globe Industrial Estate,
Dukinfield, Cheshire, SK16 4UU,
United Kingdom
+44 161 343 7005
sales@specialpipingmaterials.com
Scotland
Special Piping Materials (Scotland) Ltd
Moss Road, Gateway Business Park,
Aberdeen,
AB12 3GQ
+44 1224 245090
sales@specialpipingmaterials.co.uk
Social
Accreditations
Quick LinksHome
About Us
Blog
Special Piping Materials INC
4615, Kennedy Commerce Drive,
Houston,
Texas-77032
+1 281-372-6620
+1 281-372-6456
sales@specialpipingmaterialsusa.com
Brazil
Special Piping Materials Do Brasil Ltda.
Warehouse Stock & Office
Estrada do Mato Alto, 912
Campo Grande – RJ – CEP 23036-150
+55 (21) 3169-1295
+55 (21) 3500-5777
comercial@specialpipingmaterials.com.br
Social
Accreditations
Special Piping Materials (Singapore) Pvt Ltd
43, Kian Teck Drive,
Singapore-628856
+65 62648884
+65 62648884
sales@specialpipingmaterials.com.sg
Social
Accreditations
Quick LinksHome
About Us
Special Piping Materials Fze
P.O.Box: 120667,
Sharjah Airport Free Zone,
Sharjah – UAE
+971 50 564 0 523
+971 50 564 0 523
sales@specialpipingmaterials.ae
Oman
Special Piping Materials
Authorised representative for Oman
Petrovision International LLC,
PB NO: 1497, Postal Code 133,
Al Khuwair, Oman.
http://www.petrovisiongroup.com
+968 24 482 137
+968 24 482 158
rajesh@petrovisiongroup.com
Social
Accreditations
Quick LinksHome
About Us
Project Management
© Copyright 2020. Special Piping Materials.Website Design by Numagoo
Privacy Policy
UK Terms and Condition of Sale
UK Terms and Condition for the Purchase of Goods
Cookies on this website
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue without changing your settings, we'll assume that you are happy to receive all cookies from this website. If you would like to change your preferences you may do so by following the instructions here.
I Accept More InfoPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
